《打工姐妹花》前情提要
Previously on "2 Broke Girls"...
我选择将这场灾难当做一个启示
I am choosing to take this disaster as a sign,
在他们重建这里的时候
and while they're rebuilding this place
我要去给兰迪惊喜 重建我们感情
I'm gonna go surprise Randy and try to rebuild us!
行吧 开我的车去
Fine, use my car,
但必须是我来驾驶 我要跟你去
but I'm going to be driving it. I'm coming with you.
我好不容易才把短腿油门辅助器调到位
I finally got the gas pedal extension where I like it.
我在这等保险公司来拖车就行
I'll just call AAA.
那太好啦 再见 拜拜
Cool. Later, hater.
等等 你们真的一走了之啊
Wait, you're really leaving?
什么人会把别人就这么丢在
Who leaves someone on the side of the road
荒郊野岭的路边啊
in the middle of nowhere?
但是我的朋友邋遢乔有一台单引擎飞机
My friend, Sloppy Joe, has a one-engine plane.
他或许有办法载你们飞去洛杉矶
He might be able to fly y'all all the way to LA.
我们在奥斯丁 德克萨斯州拍摄的第一天
Well, that's a wrap on the first day of filming
就到此结束啦
here in Austin, Texas.
等等 所以兰迪不在洛杉矶吗
So Randy's not in Los Angeles?
他是在德州
He's in Texas?
麦克斯 你真是个蹩脚的跟踪狂
Wow, you're a bad stalker, Max.
我邋遢平生有两件事不做
There's two things the Slop won't do.
告知相关单位我的飞行模式
Alert the proper authorities of my flight pattern
以及踏进德克萨斯州
or step foot in Texas.
我在这里放你们下
I'll drop you here.
我答应跟你横越全国
When I agreed to follow you cross-country
去千里寻男友时
to chase your ex-boyfriend,
我没想到我会被扔下飞机
I didn't realize I'd be thrown out of a plane,
像拾荒般到处捡我的东西
scavenging for my belongings
还得跟一条蛇抢我最爱的裤子
and fighting a snake for my favorite pants.
您留着吧 蛇先生
You can have them, sir!
找到我的牙刷啦
Ah! Found my toothbrush.
麦克斯 太恶心了吧
Max, that's disgusting.
好像是有点恶心 这不是我的
Oh, you're right. This isn't mine.
找到个包包
Ah, found a purse...
上面有根针筒
Under this syringe.
针筒里有东西吗
Anything in there?
基本都空了 真是太倒霉了
Nah, pretty tapped out, which is too bad
你可以睡一场两天长的海洛因觉
'cause you could use a two-day heroin nap.
我是说我包里
I meant my bag.
你看还有什么幸免于难
Look what else survived!
我的薯片
My Popchips!
它在劫难逃的是我的肚子
Only to meet an unfortunate end.
惨了 麦克斯 我的钱包
Oh, no, Max, my wallet.
是啊 是很惨
Mm, yeah, I know.
你比驾照那张照片 老了不是一点半点
You've aged a lot since that license picture.
是钱包丢了
No, it's gone.
我们所有的现金跟信用卡都在里面呢
All of our cash and our credit cards were in there.
我们该怎么办 我要抓狂了
What are we gonna do? I'm freaking out.
别别别 先冷静
Nah, nah, nah, calm down.
卡洛琳会想办法救我们的
Caroline will get us out of this.
等等 你就是卡洛琳
Oh, wait. You're Caroline.
我要打给餐厅求救了
I'm calling the diner for help.
阿憨... 我... 有...
Han... We... have..
卡洛琳 我们信号[关系]不好
Caroline, we don't have a good connection,
不单是因为我们俩天蝎座相冲
and not just because we're dueling Scorpios.
躲猫猫
Peek-a-boo!
我看到你啦
I see you!
奥列格
Oleg.
好啦 现在跟芭芭拉这么玩吧
All right, now do it with Barbara.
阿憨 我们所有的私人物品
Han, we had all of our belongings
全被从私人飞机上扔下去了
thrown out of a private plane.
卡洛琳 你的信号断断续续
Caroline, you're cutting out.
我只听见"私人飞机" 你个臭显摆
All I heard was "private plane" brag much?
不是 我们需要去到德州
No, we need to get to Texas,
你能往我支付宝里打五百块吗
so can you please put $500 in my PayPal account?
什么 你有五百块吗
What? You have $500?
我买这件酷炫背心时 有打给你炫耀吗
Did I call you to gloat when I bought this snazzy new vest?
我要开免提
I'm putting you on speaker.
私人飞机...
Private plane...
有... 信用卡
Have...credit card...
断线了
We lost her.
或者是她的管家把她电话抢走了
Or maybe her butler snatched her phone from her.
他挂电话了
He hung up.
麦克斯 我们能回去我们称为家的那地狱吗
Max, can we just go back to that terrible place we call home?
那只美洲狮在穿我的新衣服了
That mountain lion is wearing my new blouse.
她追来啦
And here she comes!
你想退钱的话 记得留着吊牌
Keep the tags on if you wanna return it.
我要打给信用卡公司
I'm calling the credit card company
让他们给我们寄新卡
to send us new cards.
他们已经习惯听我哭了
They're used to hearing me cry.
我们看《疯狂动物城》时
So is the unfortunate family
坐后面的一家人也听习惯了
that sat behind us at "Zootopia."
连动物间都能当好朋友 我们也行
If animals can all get along, so can we.
等我们拿到新卡
Look, once we get our cards,
我们就能继续上路去德州找兰迪
we'll be on our way to Randy in Texas--
这整件事对我有啥好处来着呢
and what was in this for me again?
5.5次濒死经验吗
5 1/2 near-death experiences?
信用卡公司 是我 卡洛琳
Hi, Visa. It's me, Caroline.
我的卡被偷了
My cards were stolen.
我在一些面包车的后车厢
I've seen backs of vans
看过的糖果种类都比你店里好
with better candy selections.
你们真是丢了"有油又有吃"这店名
This is a disgrace to the name Gas and Gobble.
你每天哪来的动力起床啊
How do you even wake up in the morning?
被我的鳄鱼舔脸舔醒的
My alligator licks my face.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max.
偷我们卡的人 把我们卡刷爆了
Whoever stole our credit cards maxed them out.
把我们所剩的1500花完了
They spent the $1,500 we had left.
不是吧
No way.
刚刚才有人花了1500块买手机卡跟香烟
Someone just spent $1,500 on phone cards and cigarettes.
他的名字叫卡洛琳·钱宁
His name was Caroline Channing.
什么
What?
那是我的名字
That's my name!
你有个男人的名字啊
Ah, you got a dude's name.
我们被抢了 警察叔叔
Ugh, we were robbed. Police!
-哪里 -哪里
- Where! - Where!
麦克斯 我又累又饿
Max, I am tired and I'm hungry
而且找不到个镜子
and I can't find a mirror,
但我感觉到头发部位有"乱流"
but I am sensing a disturbance in my hair.
我们得回家了
We have to go home!
但我们必须去德州啊
But we have to go to Texas.
兰迪需要我
Randy needs me.
他在快拍上说了
He's saying it on his Snapchat story.
还在电影片场
Still on the movie set.
挺寂寞 如果有人愿意
Pretty lonely, so if anyone would respond
接受我手机拼字游戏的邀请
to my Words With Friends request,
我答应放水让你赢
I promise to let you win,
如果你来德州了
and if you're ever in Texas...
何苦啊
why?
你看 他在求我去找他
See? He's begging me to come there.
但我们没钱去那里啊
But we have no money to get to Texas.
错了
Wrong.
我这半边里藏了11块
I've got $11 in this one
这边藏了32块
and $32 in this one.
左边跟平常一样留了一手
Lefty's been holding back as per usual.
所以你的这43块奶钱
So your 43 boob dollars
能让我们去到德州吗
are gonna get us to Texas?
还有我的菊花硬币呢
Don't rule out my roll of butt quarters.
汗水淋淋但准备就绪
Sweaty but ready.
你们能帮忙关店吗
All right, can y'all folks lock up?
我得赶在内河船
I got to make a riverboat
出发去新奥尔良之前上船
before it takes off to New Orleans.
我的亲戚蒂姆给我下降头了
My cousin Tim put a voodoo curse on me.
我得去跟他谈谈 让他帮我弄掉
I got to talk to him about removing it.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
新奥尔良离德州挺近
New Orleans is close to Texas.
我的麦当劳桌垫上的汉堡神偷是这么说的
The Hamburglar says so on my McDonald's placemat,
他这人从不说谎
and he would never lie
除非是为了偷好吃的汉堡时才会
unless it's about stealing delicious hamburgers.
我有点迷糊了 你是想吃汉堡
I'm confused. Do you want hamburgers
还是想去搭内河船
or do you wanna take that riverboat?
很明显 最好的情况就是两者皆是
Obviously, the dream scenario is both.
多谢
Ah, thank you very much.
麦克斯 上船要票的
Max, people have tickets.
你得付钱才能上这...
You have to pay to get on this--
我挺确定会是我第六次濒死经验
what I'm positive will be my sixth near-death experience.
转身弯腰 松开菊花
So bend over and unclench.
你的菊花硬币也得用上
We need those butt quarters.
你是带我去参加教堂嘉年华时的我妈吗
Who are you? My mother at a church carnival?
请准备好您的船票
Have your tickets ready, please.
我们表现得不突兀就行了
All we have to do is act like we belong.
那我能装出我可爱的南方口音吗
Do I at least get to have an adorable Southern accent?
不许装口音
No accent.
我表四
Well, I do declare
这真素太令人苏望啦
that is mighty disappointing.
学着点 是时候对陌生人伸魔爪啦
Just follow my lead. It's time to touch strangers.
你的双枪[二头肌]有持枪证吗
Hey, you got a permit for those guns?
我说
Well, I say,
你有许可证...
you got a permit for
来携带那发光溜溜球吗
that light-up yo-yo?
我有女朋友了
I have a girlfriend.
少废话 臭小鬼
Keep walking, buster.
麦克斯 这船到新奥尔良要两天呢
Max, the riverboat doesn't get to New Orleans for two days
我们没地方睡啊
and we have nowhere to sleep.
但是这船上有
Ooh, but there is
"自己做斑鸠琴"课 在五点
a "Whittle Your Own Banj" workshop at 5:00.
我对这"班就"一点兴趣都没有
I have whittle-to-no interest in that.
上面写这里有最好赢的老虎机[最荡的妞]
Ooh, it says they have the loosest slots around.
看来我老家的浪货达比姐妹也在船上
I guess the Darby sisters from my hometown are here.
我看到那边的沼泽展览区
I did see a bunch of lounge chairs
有不少躺椅
over by the swamp exhibit.
我猜我们今晚可以试着在那里睡
I guess we could sleep there tonight,
至于明天晚上呢
and then the next night,
好运的话 到时候我们已经死了呢
well, hopefully we'll be dead.
来吧 红
Come on, red!
麦克斯 不可以 这是我们所有的钱
Max, no! That's all of our money!
停止下注
No more bets.
这太蠢了
Oh, that is so stupid,
而且不是像上次
and not cute stupid like
你以为尼龙搭扣是大自然产生的那种蠢萌
when you thought Velcro grew in nature.
红色赢
And red is the winner.
哎哟妈呀
Well, rootin' tootin'!
永远赌红色 因为我的姓是布莱克[黑]
I always bet on red because my last name's Black,
而我从来就不是一位赢家
and that's ah-not been a winner.
现在我们的钱变双倍了
Okay, now that we've doubled our money,
-或许该收手了 -来吧 红色
- maybe we should stop. - Come on, red!
-停止下注 -不要啊
- No more bets. - No!
你输光前我都还没来得及摸摸它们呢
I didn't even get to touch it before you lost it.
你为什么要拒绝拥有呢
Why do you hate having things?
红色连庄
Red again.
请叫我雨神 因为要下钱雨啦
Just call me Al Roker 'cause I'm making it rain.
麦克斯 我们居然在某事上能赢
Max, we're winning at something.
别光站着像个花瓶啊 小美人
Don't just stand there looking pretty, toots.
给干爹点几个鸡翅膀
Order daddy some wings.
天啊 我像个花瓶吗
Oh, my God, I look pretty
而且还能伸手叫服务员来
and I get to flag down a waitress.
服务员
Waitress!
我要来一杯沙士
I'll have a sarsaparilla
然后一些鸡翅膀给我的干爹
and some wings for big daddy.
苏菲打来了
Sophie's calling.
老娘怎么可能接
Pfft, like I'm gonna get it.
卡洛琳不接电话
Well, Caroline's not answering.
行政决策
Executive decision.
马可以吃布丁
Horses can eat a bunch of pudding.
我切尔诺贝利的表亲有只这大小的狗
My cousin from Chernobyl had a dog this size.
他有三条腿
He had three legs.
我是说我表亲 不是那条狗
My cousin, not the dog.
切尔诺贝利事件还是有好的一面嘛
Something good did come out of Chernobyl.
不好意思
Excuse me?
跟他拍照要多少钱呢
How much do you charge for pictures with him?
得看情况了
Oh, it depends.
你想要他裸露到什么程度
How nude do you want him?
我是说我们的孩子...
We mean for our kids...
跟马拍照
with the horse.
不需要发出"恶"的声音吧
I don't think the "Ew" was necessary.
你完全不知道你错过了什么好料
You don't know what you're missing.
我们只是帮忙朋友遛个马
I mean, we're just walking him for our friend.
一个孩子十块钱
We'll give you $10 each.
中标的是这位
Sold to the woman who...
"不愿"看到我裸体的女士
"doesn't" wanna see me naked.
来吧 18
Come on, 18!
这数字也是我出道的那部成人片名
Which is also the title of my adult film debut.
拿我的那部估计会取
Mine would have been called,
"这又何妨 都24岁了"
"Might As Well, I'm 24"
抱歉 胡子先生
Excuse me, Mr. Moustache?
你能别用你的脚趾骚扰我的脚踝了吗
Could you stop feeling my ankle with your toes?
看来是不愿意的意思
I guess that's a no.
18号 赢
Oh, 18 winner.
我们赢啦 我有钱啦
We won! I'm rich!
现在你跟老娘没戏了
Now you have no shot with me.
别走远 小宝贝 你是幸运女神
Stay close, sweet cakes. You're good luck.
给 兄弟 给你自己买双新拖鞋
Here, buddy. Buy yourself some new sandals,
再请在座各位来杯漱口水
and a round of mouthwash for the table.
好啦 请下注
All right, place your bets.
我当年下注到了人文科学学位
I placed mine on a liberal arts degree.
所以才沦落至此
That's why I'm here.
上啊
Let it ride.
麦克斯 或许我们该见好就收
Max, maybe we should quit while we're ahead
毕竟咱们从来没"好"过
since we've never been before.
难道你就不担心我们会...
Aren't you worried that we might...
18号连庄
18 again!
赢个不停 死都死不了吗
Keep winning and never die!
这次下4吧
Let's go with four.
是打从我上了这艘船
The number of men who have flashed me
暴露狂露鸟给我看的次数
since I've been on this riverboat.
幸运4号
Lucky four!
下好离手
No more bets.
谁开的船啊
Who's driving this thing?
加里·布希吗
Gary Busey?
4号 没有赢家
Oh, four. No winners.
有赢家啊 我们下的4号
Yes, winners. We had four,
但船刚才害我们的筹码移动了
but then the boat moved our chips.
还害我的汽水撒了呢
Yeah, and it also spilled my soda.
就像我所说的 没有赢家
So like I said: No winners.
好吧 我们输光了所有钱
Sure, we lost all our money,
可至少你看了好几个人的鸟啊
but at least you got to see some dongs.
苏菲 是我卡...
Hey, Sophie, it's me Car--ah!
我每次都被她
I fall for her...
"安安 我是苏菲"
"Hello, this is Sophi"
那条电话录音给骗了
outgoing message every time.
我们得让他们赶紧转钱过来
We need them to send that money.
谢天谢地 苏菲 我是...
Oh, thank God. Hi, Sophie, it's--
这是什么情况
What's going on here?
你们是在出卖栗宝的肉体让人骑吗
Are you selling pony rides with Chestnut?
是的 但你也得跟其他孩子一样排队
Yes, but you got to wait in line with the other kids.
不 你不用 伙计
No, you don't, buddy.
我抱你上马吧
Up you go, champ.
放我下来
Get your hands off me!
人家不想拍照
I don't want my picture taken!
暂时不想
Right now.
姑娘们让我确保栗宝不会饿肚子
The girls asked me to make sure you're feeding him,
而你们却当起了皮条客 让他出来卖就像...
and here you are pimping him out like...
这不是我的专业范畴
this isn't my wheelhouse.
有人认识著名的皮条客吗
Famous pimps, anyone?
什么
What?
她们俩居然敢不相信我们
How dare they not trust us.
这事就此打住吧
This stops now!
除非你的小兄弟阿憨
Unless your boy, Han,
能在这场"马戏"中拿到一点甜头
gets a little taste of the horse-play.
拿去
Here.
这是什么情况
What's going on here?
没情况
Nothing.
我一眼就能看出见不得人的勾当
I know a shady deal when I see one.
我可是当时对路易斯安娜购地案反对声最大的人之一啊
I was one of the loudest voices against the Louisiana Purchase.
厄尔 你跑来这里干什么
Earl, what are you even doing here?
我以为你的活动范围仅限餐厅呢
I thought you lived at the diner.
还好姑娘们让阿憨监督你们的同时
Well, thank God the girls asked me to check on Han
让我监督阿憨
checking on you too
因为现在这位黑人老兄
'cause now this black male
准备黑心地敲诈你们了
is about to blackmail you.
好吧 厄尔也分一份
Okay, Earl's in too.
但他的分成少点 因为可能等下
At a lesser percentage because odds are
他就会忘掉这里发生的一切
he'll forget about all of this momentarily.
麻烦过来一下 经理
Excuse me, manager.
我们受到不公正的对待
We've been wronged,
不仅仅是我们的日常生活
and not just generally by life.
我都不知道那该跟谁投诉了
I don't know who to complain to about that.
请问有什么问题吗
Is there a problem over here?
我是赌场经理
I'm the pit boss.
也是总统刺客舞厅
I also do the mentalist show
心灵感应秀的主持人
in the John Wilkes Booth Ballroom.
演出还有很多票哦
Still lots of tickets available.
是的 的确出了点问题
Yes, there's a problem here.
我们赌桌上赢来的钱都被骗走了
We just got cheated out of our winnings,
我20多岁的人生中已经被夺走很多东西了
and I was already cheated out of much of my 20s,
但那可能不在你的管辖范围
but again, probably not your department.
不如我免费赠送你们一瓶香槟作为赔礼
Why don't I send a complimentary bottle of champagne
送到你们房间可好
to your room?
我说的"香槟"是红酒
And by "champagne" I mean wine,
"一瓶"是指一盒
and by "bottle" I mean box.
不劳烦了 我们在这里喝吧
Uh, you know what? We'll take it here.
不会恰好是便利店的盒装垃圾红酒吧
Would there happen to be a 7 Eleven Merlot?
麦克斯 在房间里喝红酒听上去惬意多了
Max, wine in our room sounds so much better.
我们可以放轻松 沉浸在两人世界里
We can relax and focus on each other for once.
太好了 你们房间号是多少
Mm, great. What's the room number?
她是想说06号
I think she means oh-six.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
那房间现在还是封锁的犯罪现场呢
That room is still an active crime scene.
逃票上船的吧
Stowaways, huh?
我马上叫海岸警卫队来抓你们
I'll have the Coast Guard come and pick you up.
他们刚去抓那家伙
They're already coming for that guy.
不是我自己要扒光衣服
I didn't wanna strip my clothes off
去开这艘船的
and try to drive the boat.
我是被人下降头了
It was that voodoo curse.
都怪你 蒂姆
Damn you, Tim!
听着 兄弟 如果你真会心灵感应
Look, dude, if you're really a mentalist,
你就会知道我真的得去德州见我男朋友
you'll know that I need to get to Texas to see my boyfriend.
我感应到你说的是实话
I can tell that you're telling the truth.
求你了 肯定有办法能解决
Please, there has got to be a way we can work something out.
我们什么都愿意做
We'll do anything.
她啥都愿意 我只做保留上衣蹭的那种
Well, she will. I'll do over the shirt stuff.
你的上衣
Your shirt.
前提是你把帽子脱掉
If you take off that hat.
这世界上有没有一个地方
Is there anywhere in the world
可以让我摆脱服务员这个职业
where I don't have to be a waitress?
波霸餐厅
Hooters?
多谢安慰
Thanks.
老娘是密西西比河上的鸡尾酒服务员
I'm a cocktail waitress on the Mississippi River.
真是超级悲催
This is a worse vacation
比有艾德·赫尔姆斯的假期还惨
than the one with Ed Helms in it.
抱歉 先生
Sorry, sir.
想找个手机信号好的地方
Looking for some cell service.
不如我坐你大腿 你带我四处转转如何
Hey, why don't I sit in your lap and you can drive me around?
一举两得哦
Two birds, one stone?
老娘也没那么稀罕你好吗
I wasn't that attracted to you anyway.
我要去找个有手机信号的地方
I'm gonna go try to find some reception.
看到兰迪惨兮兮是现在唯一
Seeing Randy miserable is the only thing
能让我乐呵呵的事情
that'll cheer me up right now.
没准他在哭鼻子呢
Maybe he's crying.
一杯伏特加给脖子有纹身的男士
One vodka for the gentleman with the neck tattoo,
两杯伏特加是给这位女士
and two vodkas for the lady
一看你就好这口
who's into that sort of thing.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的鲶鱼沙拉塔马上就来
Your catfish tower's on its way.
各种酱料需要两个人才搬得动
It takes two to carry the cocktail sauce lagoon.
全压00
Everything on double-zero.
这艘船在点评网上的评分肯定也是这数
Which has to be the Yelp rating of this boat.
麻烦一下
Excuse me?
能给我来杯白葡萄汽酒吗
Could I get a white wine spritzer?
别这样嘛 薇拉 我们共用一个衣橱呢
Oh, come on, Vera. We share a locker.
开 00
Oh, double-zero.
赢家
Winner.
太棒了 我又成为赢家了
Yes, I'm a winner again!
服不服 船客们
Suck it, river people.
这是怎么回事
What is going on over here?
员工不允许参加赌博
Employees are not allowed to gamble.
或性骚扰其他员工 上周刚出的条例
Or, as of last week, sexually harass each other.
你的"功劳"啊 克雷格
Thanks a lot, Craig.
无线电室的波因德克斯特
Poindexter in the radio room
死都不让我用卫星电话
wouldn't let me use the satellite phone.
对了 我把你的卫星电话弄坏了
Also, I broke your satellite phone.
真是够了 你们被解雇了
That is it. You're fired.
这是自"你们被录用了"后
That's the worst news I've heard
我听到最"糟糕"的消息了
since you said "You're hired."
有艘拖船要来换厕所排泄物
There's a tug coming to swap out the toilet tanks.
我要把你俩扔上去
I am putting you two on it.
去当船长吗
As captains?
或是我该说 屎长
Or should I say, crap-tains?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我给芭芭拉的婴儿车换上了旋转轮毂
I got spinning wheels for Barbara's carriage.
现在牛气的可不止她的脾气了
Now's it's not just her attitude that's gangster.
拜托 你们能不能小声点
Uh... can y'all keep it down, please?
我在试着弄我的新无线耳机呢
I'm trying to set up my new wireless headphones.
我要让我的随身听音质变牛逼
Gonna make my WalkMan sound amazing.
真是太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
我一直试图保持低调
I'm trying to keep things on the down-low,
而你们仨却跑去大肆挥霍疯狂购物
and you three went on the biggest shopping spree
就像主持人艾伦去男装连锁店一样
since Ellen at a Men's Wearhouse sale.
等等
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
阿憨 你怎么会比柜台还高
Han, why are you taller than the counter?
因为我饮食恰当 睡眠充足
Just been eating right and getting enough sleep.
是啊 有古怪
Yeah, something's weird.
你跟一只成年企鹅差不多高
You're almost the height of an adult penguin.
好啦 我给自己买了内增高
Fine! I treated myself to lifts.
我受够在地铁上鼻子贴别人屁股的窘境
I was sick of being nose to butt with everyone on the subway.
快看卡洛琳的图片分享网
Check out Caroline's Instagram.
貌似她们这次真的有大麻烦
Looks like they're in more trouble than I was
比我上次想穿上工装裤还麻烦
the last time I tried to put on overalls.
她们在一艘都是排泄物的拖船上
Ooh, they're on a tugboat filled with toilets,
她写道"救我
and she writes, "Help.
拜托快转钱"
Please send money."
我该...
So...
快速取消关注吗
quick unfollow?
或者考虑一晚 明天一早帮她们祈祷
Or sleep on it and pow-wow in the morning?
不 我们必须救她们
No. We have to help them.
反正我耳机的线也弄丢了
I lost the cord to these headphones anyway.
蹲厕所腿麻的毛病在船上也一样
Oh, still got toilet boat legs.
这地方散发这一股恶臭
Ugh, this place reeks of bait.
不 等等 是我自己 我嘴巴张着呢
Oh, no, wait. That was me. My mouth was open.
更重要的是
More importantly,
我手机终于有信号了
I finally have enough bars on my phone
可以上网追踪兰迪了
to stalk Randy on Snapchat.
真棒 我们所有问题都解决了
Oh, great! All of our problems are solved,
除了没食物没钱 连睡觉的地方都没有之外
except for food, money, and a place to sleep.
好负能量哦
So negative.
你难道没看见这无人看守的
Have you not seen the sneeze-guard-less
鱼饵店沙拉吧吗
bait shop salad bar?
说到可悲
Speaking of pathetic,
让我先看看我们家可怜的兰迪
let me just check in on poor Randy.
又是一个在德州的孤独夜
Just another lonely night here in Texas...
跟我的一帮新朋友共度
with all my new best friends!
扭扭乐该轮到我了 不许插队
Hey! I was up next for Twister!
杰克真贱
Classic Jake.
我确定他只是强颜欢笑
I'm sure he's just putting on a happy face.
不然哪里忍受得了杰克这种人
That's obviously the only way to handle Jake.
我能看出他内心深处其实真的很难过
Deep down, I can tell he's genuinely upset.
我现在真的很开心
I'm just genuinely happy right now.
这沙拉吧臭死了
Ugh, this salad bar stinks.
不 等等 还是我自己的味道
No, wait. That's me again.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max!
餐厅的人把钱转到我们的支付宝账户了
The diner people put money in our PayPal account!
他们说是栗宝给的
They say it's from Chestnut,
但我们不在家 他是不准上网的
but he's not allowed on the Internet when we're not home.
真是难以置信
I can't believe it.
我也是
Me neither.
在这世界上 我们穷得只剩餐厅这帮人
The diner people are all we have in this world.
想当初我富的时候 有个专门放丝巾的衣橱呢
And I used to have a closet just for scarves.
不 是没有我兰迪照样开心
No! That Randy's happy without me.
我这是干什么
What am I doing?
我拖着你跑遍整个国家
I'm dragging you all over the country
就为了某个对我不再感兴趣的家伙
after some guy who isn't even interested in me anymore.
这是我告诉德尼罗坚持演喜剧后最糟糕的主意
This is my worst idea since I told DeNiro to stick to comedy.
你想说什么
So, what are you saying?
我想说 这是一个错误
I'm saying this is a mistake.
我们还是按你之前
Let's just go home like you said
被土狼撞倒在地试图侵犯你时
after that hyena knocked you to the ground
所说的那样 回家吧
and tried to hump you.
四号餐你能12块卖给我吗
Can I get $12 on number four?
哪条通道有带褶皱的胶带卖
And on which aisle can I find tucking tape?
好吧 那我就买点牛肉棒和巧克力蛋糕吧
Okay, I will just have these Slim Jims and a Ho-Ho.
反正我今天也不用把自己硬塞进时装里
It's not like I have to fit into couture today.
-不许打我 -不许打我
- Stop hitting me. - Stop hitting me!
姑娘们 别打了
Girls, stop fighting.
我讨厌看见女人打架
I hate to see women fighting each other.
当然 除非是霍达和凯西·李
Well, unless, of course, it's Hoda and Kathie Lee
为了最后一杯白葡萄酒大打出手
over the last glass of chardonnay.
是鲁保罗
That's RuPaul!
《鲁保罗变装皇后秀》的那个
From RuPaul's Drag Race!
我们超爱看你的秀 我们之前都
We love your show. We used to watch it
从我们邻居杰夫的窗户看
through our neighbor Jeff's window.
但他后来跟迪恩好上了
But then he met Dean,
现在他们俩整天不穿衣服做饭
and now all they do is cook naked.
所以我们现在就看裸男秀了
So we just watch that now.
你们俩小可怜
Oh, you poor babies.
你们俩为什么打架
So, why the cat fight?
她是不是偷了你46码的高跟鞋
Did she steal your size 12 stilettos?
要是我肯定会揍死那个贱人
'Cause I would cut a bitch for that.
我们其实是在去德州的路上
We were actually on our way to Texas
看看她和她前男友能不能重修旧好
to see if she and her ex could patch things up.
不 我们不去德州了
No, we're not going to Texas.
我们要回家
We're going back home.
有时你不得不承认自己的失败...
Sometimes you got to admit defeat...
这通心粉沙拉里有一只鲜活的小甲虫
and that there is a very live junebug in this macaroni salad.
不 亲爱的 我不喜欢失败的声音
Oh, no, honey. I do not like the sound of defeat.
你们想知道如果我放弃梦想 我会在哪里吗
You want to know where I'd be if I'd given up on my dreams?
住在马路的尽头
Living right down the road
开一家女性服饰店
managing a Dress Barn,
穿着舞会礼服 开400英里远去唱卡拉OK
driving 400 miles in a ball gown to sing karaoke.
我不会成为世界超模
I would not be the supermodel of the world
也就是今日的我
that I am today,
好咩
okay?
懂没
Hello.
听着 我正好开车去德州
Hey, listen. I'm driving to Texas
你们想搭顺风车吗
if y'all want a ride.
那我们一起华丽丽离开吧
Well, shall we sashay away?
你知道这话是有版权的
You know that's copyrighted.
再说的话 我可要收你1万2的版权费哦
Say it again, and you owe me $12,000.
我坐前排
Shotgun!
我要坐鲁保罗旁边
I'm sitting next to RuPaul!
不 我要坐鲁保罗旁边
No. I'm sitting next to RuPaul.
-我要坐鲁保罗旁边 -我要...
- I'm sitting next to RuPaul. - I am...